{
    "subject": "resource/Arizona_Territory",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Phoenix,_Arizona",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Arizona Territory is Phoenix, Arizona.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.950648844242096,
            "question": "What is the capital of Arizona Territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9329068660736084,
            "question": "Which state had Phoenix as its capital territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9295997023582458,
            "question": "What is the name of the capital city of Arizona Territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8909964561462402,
            "question": "Is Phoenix still the capital of Arizona?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8147864937782288,
            "question": "What other cities were considered for the capital of Arizona Territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731967568397522,
            "question": "When was Phoenix established as the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6167048215866089,
            "question": "How has Phoenix grown since it became the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.559059739112854,
            "question": "Where is Phoenix located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44082653522491455,
            "question": "What is significant about Phoenix's role as a historical capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3607102930545807,
            "question": "What factors influenced the decision to make Phoenix the capital?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Arizona Territory is Phoenix, Arizona.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9324_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is significant about Phoenix's role as a historical capital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9324_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Phoenix located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9324_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Phoenix grown since it became the capital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9324_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9324_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Prescott became the first capital of Arizona Territory in 1864, Tucson was the capital from 1867-1877, and then Prescott again until Phoenix became the capital in 1889."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The capital of Arizona is Phoenix\" and provide additional details about its history as the capital of Arizona Territory. Therefore, the statement \"The capital of Arizona Territory is Phoenix, Arizona\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}